https://www.andysmall.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Home / Privacy Policy
This privacy policy describes how we collect, use, transfer and disclose personally identifiable information (“personal information”) that we may obtain about you through this website.
1) This website (https://www.andysmall.co.uk/) is owned and operated by Andy Small Fine Art Photography.
2) This website is hosted by third party service providers on servers located in the UK. Personal information is gathered, stored and processed using servers located in the UK and the United States. By using this website or submitting any personal information to Andy Small Fine Art Photography, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by this privacy policy.
3) Personal information is gathered and managed by Andy Small Fine Art Photography in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998 and the GDPR. Andy Small Fine Art Photography endeavours to keep all personal information up to date, and manages appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personal information we hold.
4) If Andy Small Fine Art Photography holds your contact details, we will use them only for contacting you in connection with any enquiry or other request you have made.
5) Andy Small Fine Art Photography will not sell or transfer your contact details on to third parties, except if required to by law.
6) By making any enquiry or other request, you agree that Andy Small Fine Art Photography can access, process and retain any personal information that you give us for the purposes of managing your enquiry or request.
7) In order to request a quote, you must opt-in to give your consent to receive information from Andy Small Fine Art Photography.
8) If Andy Small Fine Art Photography holds your contact details, you have the right to find out what those details are, to have your details updated or corrected, or to have them removed from our database. Please email info@andysmall.co.uk, and your request will be actioned upon receipt.
9) Andy Small Fine Art Photography uses only cookies of Category 1 (strictly necessary) and Category 2 (performance) which are anonymous and aggregated. No personal data is stored or tracked. Category 3 (functionality) and Category 4 (targeting or advertising) cookies are not used on this website. By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
10) This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service by Google (www.google.com/policies/privacy) Information about your use of this website is collected via cookies and transferred to and stored on servers of Google located in the US and elsewhere.
11) Andy Small Fine Art Photography does not use tracking links in any email messages that we may send to you.
12) Nothing in this privacy policy affects any rights you or Andy Small Fine Art Photography may have under data protection legislation.
Search for:
Search
Contact Andy
You can reach Andy using the contact page, or alternatively you can email andy@andysmall.co.uk.
View all upcoming shows and exhibitions.
View all upcoming talks and courses.
Copyright © - Andy Small.
